GOOD DETECTIVE KANG PIL-GU 5
"LIM HYEON-JUN'S SUDDEN CONFESSION"
"HE FIRMLY DENIES DATING GWON SE-NA"
LIM HYEON-JUN
"WHO IS KANG PIL-GU'S WOMAN?"
SOME SAY LIM HYEON-JUN'S GIRLFRIEND
IS DIRECTOR BAK BYEONG-GI.
THEY WERE REPORTEDLY SPOTTED
DOING PILATES TOGETHER VERY CLOSELY.
AIDE WOO YOUNG-SUK'S SISTER-IN-LAW
MS. WI, CAN YOU COME
TO THE RESTAURANT TOMORROW?
SOME SAY LIM HYEON-JUN'S GIRLFRIEND
IS DIRECTOR BAK BYEONG-GI.
EPISODE 15
SPORTS EUNSEONG
NON-DISCLOSURE AGREEMENT
NOVA INVESTMENTS LTD, SHELL COMPANY
SLUSH FUND CREATION DETAIL REPORT
IMPERIAL PRINT
EUNSEONGILBO
THANK YOU
WI JEONG-SIN
WI JEONG-SIN, EUNSEONGILBO
THANK YOU
EUNSEONGILBO
WI JEONG-SIN, EUNSEONGILBO
THANK YOU
ENTERTAINMENT DESK
POLICE CODE OF CONDUCT
BEST RICE PORRIDGE
GET WELL SOON
I MISS YOU ALREADY
GOOD DETECTIVE KANG PIL-GU
BEST ACTOR AWARD
LIM HYEON-JUN
GOOD DETECTIVE KANG PIL-GU 5
EPISODE 1
PIL-GU
GOOD DETECTIVE KANG PIL-GU 5
EPISODE 1
GOOD DETECTIVE KANG PIL-GU
THANK YOU
WI JEONG-SIN, EUNSEONGILBO
SPECIAL THANKS TO OH YEON-SEO
FOR HER APPEARANCE